Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
50-year-old male. suspected stroke.
- You're his wife?
- Yes.
We'll take care of him. Bay Four.
You can't come back.
- Last known well time?
- Unknown.
- His son found him. He thinks three hours.
- Okay.
Mom. where is he?
Sweetheart. we're gonna have to wait
out here. okay?
-Wait how long?
-I don't know.
♪ Eyes of emerald and white ♪
♪ More precious than gold ♪
♪ Hands as soft as the sand ♪
♪ But harder to hold ♪
♪ But till the day I die ♪
♪ I will dream of you ♪
♪ In a million lives ♪
♪ You're the one… ♪
Cole. can you run home?
- Dad's gonna need some stuff.
- I can do it.
You guys should stay here. I'll be back.
♪ I'll love you ♪
♪ Till my last breath ♪
♪ You're gone ♪
♪ But something in the heavens
Tells me that we'll be together again ♪
♪ Sounds of gathering clouds
Are all that I hear ♪
♪ Just days of permanent gray
Since you disappeared ♪
♪ But till the day I die ♪
♪ I will dream of you ♪
♪ In a million lives… ♪
You're not coming in? It's been a while.
Maybe another time.
♪ I'll love you ♪
♪ Till the last breath ♪
♪ You're gone ♪
♪ But something in the heavens
Tells me that we'll be together again ♪
♪ Together again ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Something in the heavens
Tells me that we'll be together again ♪
-Hey. guys.
-Hey. Mom.
Kids.
Everyone.
can you come down here for a second?
How is he?
He's better.
When is he coming home?
Not for a little bit.
But it's been weeks.
Dr. Segil says
he's through the worst of it.
Listen. I think this is something
we're all gonna be dealing with
for a while. So
let's all try to get back
to some version of normal.
Hey.
-Hey.
-Have you seen Nathan?
-Uh. he already left.
-What?
-He said he was gonna run to school.
-But that's so far.
Wait. where are you going?
-Uh. Erin's picking me up.
-Isaac and Lee need a ride to school.
No. they stayed at Oliver's last night.
Right.
Yeah. they have been doing
that a lot lately.
- Okay. Bye. Mom.
- Bye. honey.
Okay.
Benny. is your… show-and-tell today?
Yeah.
So you made that all by yourself?
Let me take a picture of you.
and I will send that to your dad.
Perfect. Now. can you put that in the car
and be really careful with it?
Yeah.
-Mom. have you seen my football uniform?
-Yeah?
That's today?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Um…
- I put it in your gym bag.
- Oh.
And I will pick you up
and take you there tonight.
-Okay. Thanks.
-You're the best. I have your toast.
Can you get Jordan off the computer
and get in the car?
- Yeah. Jordan!
- Thanks.
Okay. coming.
Oh God.
Pete Weber has Custard.
What?
He must have gotten out
through a hole in the fence.
Dad usually checks the fence once a week.
-I haven't even thought--
-It's okay. Mom. I'll go take a look.
Thank you.
Oh shoot. I'm gonna be late.
Oh gosh. Okay.
Guys. you're supposed to be in the car!
Can one of you just get the…
- Yeah.
- Bye!
Don't you have rodeo training?
- Uh. yeah. but…
- I can check.
I have a free period first thing.
Right.
Thanks.
I gotta go.
Oh. Uh…
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Um…
Are you okay?
You've been at the hospital
every night this week.
Yeah. my mom needed a break.
And I want to be there. so…
Well. I could give you a ride to school
if… you're too tired to drive.
I have to check the fence first.
but then I--
I don't know
if I'm making it to school today.
Yeah. I'm going back to the hospital. so…
But you were just there.
I don't want him to be alone.
Yeah. I… I get that.
How is he?
I… I feel so bad
that I… I haven't seen him.
Well. you could. uh…
you could come with me.
Yeah. I… I just…
I don't like hospitals.
Yeah. yeah. I mean…
Who does?
Right. Um…
My… my parents and… and Lucy
were taken to a hospital.
-Jackie. I'm sorry. I didn't know.
-No. I know.
I know. It's all right.
You sure you're okay?
Don't worry about me.
I'm good.
You know. I. um…
I meant what I said.
That night.
Yeah.
So did I.
You know that. right?
Yeah. I do.
-But--
-But we can't.
I mean. not with your… your dad
and Alex and just everything.
- Yeah.
- It's just. it's not the right time.
Yeah. right.
Anyways. I… I gotta…
Yeah.
- Hey. Mom.
- Hi. honey.
Did you manage to sign
that paperwork I sent you?
Paperwork?
For Little Cap.
They want to start
moving in the equipment today.
That's today?
Yeah.
Okay if they start on the south field?
-Oh. Oh. man.
-I can ask Dad.
Oh. no. No. no. no.
We don't have to worry him.
-You can tell them it's fine.
-All right.
Honey.
your dad and I are really grateful
for all your help with this.
It's the least I can do considering
I'm the one that put him in the hospital.
What?
Well. that's not true.
Everything I put him through?
Mom.
Pushing through the plans when
he didn't want to go through with them?
Siding with Richard
because I wanted to be the big man?
Will.
this wasn't your fault.
Okay. I'm…
I'm gonna need to hear you say that.
This wasn't your fault.
-Honey.
-It wasn't my fault.
Okay.
I'm gonna let them know
it's okay to get started.
Here we go. boy!
Whoa!
- Okay. I think that's enough for today.
- Nope.
Alex.
Alex. hey. Stop.
You're hurt. You're no good to Hartford's
if you're burnt out.
I'm fine.
What? No. man. You need a break.
Come on. Let's go.
Okay.
Back so soon?
Can't stay away.
These delicious Jell-O cups? Come on.
Take all the time you need.
Thank you. Trudy.
What happened to you?
Training.
Sure you're not overdoing it?
Well. now that I'm with Hartford's.
I gotta step up my game.
Blake put herself on the line
to help me get that sponsorship. so…
Do you really have the time
for all that right now?
Hartford would give you a break. right?
- With your dad?
- I don't need a break.
My dad's getting better every day.
- Are you sure you--
- Yeah. He's gonna be home soon.
Is it something else?
I'm good.
I'll see you later.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm good.
- Cool.
- All good.
Good. Come on.
- Oh my God.
- What does he see in her?
What?
Oh. them.
Kiley. don't worry about it.
I'm not worried. I'm just tired of it.
I'll see you later.
Ow!
You're reading
Barefoot in the Park?
Hey.
This play's so great.
I can't wait for tonight.
Right. yeah. um. about that.
I'm gonna have to cancel.
I said that I'd babysit.
I… I mean. Jackie's been doing it
almost every night.
And I wanted to give her a chance
to go see my dad.
Even though Jordan's old enough.
I don't want to leave the kids alone.
Hey. Danny. it's okay.
It's the community theater in Lockwood.
It's not like Broadway.
-Yeah.
-It's no big deal.
Okay.
Let me show you this scene.
Nate.
Oh.
Hey. Sky.
How's your dad?
Um…
He's good. Yeah.
he's coming home soon. actually.
Great.
That's… great. Nathan.
You know.
if you want to take your mind off things.
you could take on the music column.
I liked the idea
you had about local bands.
What about Ramona?
She's more into school orchestra stuff.
I was thinking
we could do with something more edgy.
I don't think I can right now.
Yeah. take your time.
Just. you know.
send me something when you're ready?
Could she give us a more depressing topic?
Like. the Black Death?
The answer's in the name. Black Death.
There's not a lot of space for nuance.
Right. but I guess maybe trying to find a…
Oh. Hello.
Hi.
Hey.
You made it.
To school.
You said you might not.
Uh. yeah. I… I just stayed at the hospital
until my mom got there.
How is he?
The same.
Are you. uh… are you going back there or…
No. uh. my mom's gonna go.
I'm working at Tony's tonight.
Right.
Yeah.
So.
uh. I'll see you.
Yes. Yeah. Bye.
Bye.
Hey. You ready to go?
I… I have to go take Parker to football.
-So. uh. I'll see you tomorrow?
-Yeah. I mean. I'm always here. so…
Sure thing.
- Bye. Jackie.
- See ya.
See ya.
What was up with that?
Mmm.
Uh-huh. No. come here! Grace!
-Here's that pizza for you.
-Thank you.
Here you guys go.
Hey!
Oh my God.
- Thank you so much.
- Hey. Kiley.
Kiley. Kiley. hey.
Still worried about this?
You know. being talked about
is actually considered a perk
of being
the former football captain's girlfriend.
-It's a bit like being famous. I guess.
-I don't want to be famous.
Right.
It's fine. No. I'm… I'm fine. Uh…
Just go be with your friends.
Okay.
♪ Though nothing to say…♪
Do you think we need
to save some for Alex and Cole?
Honestly. I think they dodged a bullet.
Who sent this one?
Pete Weber brought it
when he brought Custard back.
What is it?
Grey.
Is it eggplant?
I hope so.
God. what is this?
Ugh.
Here you go. bud.
And I forgot napkins.
The website said that heavier smoothies
are easier for him to swallow.
so this has chia seeds in it.
as well as hemp and avocado.
Perfect. I will deliver that.
But I might not mention the hemp.
Or the chia.
You know. I'm gonna head over
to the hospital in a little bit.
if you wanna… join me.
Yeah. I mean. I would love to.
but I already told Danny I would babysit.
Cool.
I'll say hi for you.
Okay.
Cole.
Come here. I wanna show you something.
Pretty special. right?
This is KC Mackindson's car.
Mac's a drag racer.
Brought her in last night.
Said the… the timing was weird
in his last race.
Thinks something's off.
I've known Mac for years.
He's got a lot of cars.
So he's an important customer for us.
Well. I… I can take a look.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'd like to fix her.
Okay.
Great.
I'll let Mac know.
Hey. what are you doing here?
I thought you were babysitting.
Yeah. Jackie decided to stay home.
And honestly. I…
I just wanted to get out of the house.
You know. it's…
it's not really the same without. uh…
Hold on. Where… where were you going?
I was coming to see you.
With this.
I got it from the library.
I wanted you to feel like
you were back in New York again
to take your mind off everything.
Plus. no shade.
but I think Jane Fonda and Robert Redford
might just have the edge
on Miss Calvert. the lunch lady.
and Elwin from the gas station.
Thank you.
Come in. You hungry? My mom made dinner.
Oh. thank God. Yes.
I couldn't face another
of Ma Weber's casseroles.
Kiley.
Hey.
Come on.
I cannot believe you of all people
care what kids at school think or say.
I mean. you think most of them are idiots.
All my life. I've been under the radar.
Okay? And that's how I like it.
Okay.
Everybody's talking about us. Dylan.
So?
It's not like they're talking about
how I can do better. are they?
Just… …don't worry about it.
They're gonna get bored eventually.
I promise.
Yeah. but what if you start
to think that you could do better too?
Please.
If anybody is gonna wake up
and realize they can do better…
it's gonna be you.
I don't care what anyone thinks. Kiley.
Hey. guys!
Everybody! I made brunch!
Oh.
Wow!
Look at this.
Yeah. well. we've all been so…
It's been so long
since we all sat down together.
I thought it'd be good for us
to have brunch.
All of us.
Oh. man. there's nothing I'd love more.
but I've got a bunch of appointments.
which I would cancel in a heartbeat. but
I've been so behind
because of the hospital.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
This looks amazing.
-Did you make those?
-Mm-hmm.
From scratch. I wanted it to feel special.
It is special.
Thank you.
Oh. uh. before I forget.
I made a smoothie for George.
-It's in the fridge.
-Great! I'll grab it.
-Have fun!
-Thanks.
Parker! You can sit here.
Uh. I'm okay.
I'm actually gonna go watch TV.
-Right. But. uh…
-Yeah.
Jordan! Do you want some fruit salad?
Yeah. thanks.
- Parker. do not change that channel.
- I will if I get there first!
Hi! There is coffee. hot chocolate.
and I squeezed that juice myself.
Cool.
Okay.
-What is this?
-Um…
Guys. I was kinda hoping we could all sit…
Benny. where are you going?
Oh. I have to go check on Gregory.
This was great. Jackie.
You're leaving?
Uh. I have training.
Okay.
See you.
Cole.
Hey. Cole.
I. uh… I… I made brunch.
Oh.
Right.
Yeah. do you mind
if I take some for the guys?
The guys?
At the shop.
Yeah. I'd stay. really.
but I. um… I'm going to the hospital.
and then I gotta go to work
just after. so…
- Okay.
- Are you leaving?
Could you drop me off at band practice?
Um… Yeah. Yeah. let's go.
-Uh. Nathan. you don't want to eat first?
-Sorry. I'm so late.
Mmm.
Is Danny home?
Uh. no. I don't think so.
I think he stayed at Erin's last night.
Mmm.
It's really good. though.
Thanks.
I'm glad you're here.
How's your dad doing?
Oh. he's fine. He'll be home soon.
Okay. Let's go get ready.
Come on.
Whenever my dad comes to visit me.
it's so… weird.
It's like he thinks
I'm eight years old again.
You know.
last weekend he brought me a lollipop.
I'm sorry. Grace.
No. it's okay. I kinda like lollipops.
I don't know. It's just they both seem
so miserable without each other.
and then no one will tell me
what's going on.
You know?
Anyways.
you've been here like a hundred hours.
and all we've talked about are my parents.
so you owe me a distraction.
What's happening with Alex and Cole?
I guess you guys know
where you stand now. right?
I guess.
I mean. we're all trying to be civil. but
with everything happening with George.
it's like everything is fractured.
No one wants to be
in the same room as anybody else.
Like we're all finding it too hard
to be around each other.
And what about you and Cole?
With George and Alex and Katherine…
If Cole and I got together now. it would
blow up everything.
Like. the whole family. and…
Everybody's been through so much.
It's just not the right time.
Well. are you okay?
I just really wanted
to do something.
If I got the family to feel better
or to feel more normal
then maybe we wouldn't
all be missing George so much.
And then maybe this weirdness between
me. Alex. and Cole wouldn't feel so big.
And then maybe
I wouldn't feel so guilty all the time.
Well. there's only one way to fix that.
You have to talk to them.
Yeah. you're right.
I know you're right.
Hey.
What's going on with Murphy?
Oh yeah.
I think he's a little agitated.
It might be that hoof right there.
Okay. All right. Murphy.
I will take care of that when I get home.
- Mom.
- Yeah?
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
I'm a little bit tired. That's all.
See you later.
See ya.
So. this is from Jackie.
She said it's a healthy-fats dessert.
-See you later.
-Yeah.
Can she just not send ice cream? I mean…
-See ya.
-Bye. honey.
Thank you.
Before I go. you guys need anything?
- No.
- You sure?
- Thanks.
- All right.
- Careful going home.
- See you.
You know. Jackie should come by.
I haven't seen her at all.
It's not you. honey.
It's hospitals.
I think being here just brings back…
Oh. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Sure.
I can't say I'm too big on them
right now either.
-What?
-Nothing.
Honey. what?
I just can't stop thinking about
what if Will hadn't found you.
But he did.
Right?
- That was the worst night of my life.
- Hmm.
I thought I lost you.
Okay. well.
I am not that easy to get rid of.
I can't lose you.
-The kids can't lose you.
-Hey.
You are not losing me.
Okay?
I'm gonna be okay.
I promise.
Come on. I love you.
You okay?
No.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Dad usually does this.
You know what?
I'm just gonna… I'm gonna leave it.
Let Dad look at it when he's home.
Even when he's home. I don't think
he's gonna be able to do anything
for a while.
What? Dad?
Nah. no way. he's gonna sit on that couch
watching TV for more than. like. a day.
-Come on.
-Alex.
You know he almost died. right?
You… you get that?
He has to be okay.
I know. I…
But we gotta get used to things
being different around here.
Mom needs more help.
She… she can't go on like this.
Okay.
And Alex.
- About that night.
- Oh.
-What you heard--
-It's fine. It's fine. I get it.
I… I don't want to talk about it.
Look. you and Jackie can do what you want.
Okay? I'm over it.
Are you okay?
Does it matter?
Would it change anything?
I'm sorry I did this to you.
And you know what?
I'm sorry I feel this way.
But… I love her.
I can't… I can't stop that.
If there was…
-If there was anything I can do to--
-I know.
I know.
I love her too.
But I don't want to be with someone
who wants to be with someone else.
Dad being sick.
getting him better.
that's all that matters right now.
Just make her happy. Okay?
Okay.
Katherine.
- Hi.
- What…
Why are you doing this alone?
That is a great question.
I guess this is now my responsibility.
and I suddenly think
I should be able to fix a fence.
I don't do ranch.
I'm from New Haven. I do kids and puppies.
I birth piglets for a living.
-You could've asked one of us.
-No.
You've all been such a help.
I don't want to burden you with more.
You're not. This is too much.
Yeah. it is.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I just… I hate
that I'm not able to do more to help.
Like. I wish I could fix this.
Me too.
I wish I could fix… any of it.
I couldn't even get everyone
to sit down and eat brunch together.
I think the hardest part for us is…
admitting that we need help.
I just wish I could make it better.
Honey. I know that you've been
avoiding going to the hospital
to see George.
Yeah. um…
Being in a hospital.
it's like…
like the smell and everything.
it's… it's too hard.
I'm really sorry.
Don't apologize.
I am sorry you didn't feel like you could
come to me to help you process this.
- It's not about me.
- Yes. it is.
It's about all of us. We all get to put
ourselves first every once in a while.
Even you.
Okay.
Okay?
-I'll try.
-Okay.
You know what I need?
-What?
-A nap.
Or a smoothie. Do you have any more chia?
- I have so much chia.
- Oh!
- Can we go?
- Yeah.
-Do you want to drive?
-No!
All right. What about the grain order?
Yeah. I… I did it for next month.
And the guy said he'll set it up with you
whenever you're home.
Thanks. Cole.
You know. your mother and Will
won't tell me a thing about the ranch.
Well…
All right.
Now. you need to get out of here.
What? Are… are you good? Do you
need me to get a nurse or something?
No. no. I'm fine.
But you've been spending
too much time here.
I want to be here. Dad.
Hey. you were… you were there with me
with my knee the whole time. I…
-I wanna pay you back and be here for you.
-Look. that's not how it works.
All right? I'm the dad. and that's my job.
You… you wanna pay me back?
Then you… you get out there.
and you live your life.
All right? You don't sit around in here.
All right? I'm good.
All right? That make sense?
-Yeah.
-Then get out.
One more thing.
Oh. way better.
Oh.
That's more like it.
- I'll see you soon.
- Thanks. buddy.
Hey.
Oh. Hi.
You okay?
Yeah.
Are you?
I think I finally get
what things have been like for you.
What do you mean?
I've been so scared
about my dad.
I've been pretending
it's not been happening.
You lost everybody.
And I don't think I really understood
what that meant until now.
How do you do it?
Some days are better than others.
But. uh…
I have more good days than bad now.
so I'm doing okay.
I'm better.
It gets better.
Good.
Alex.
you know.
I… I never meant to hurt you. right?
- Or lie to you.
- Yeah. I know.
And even if you weren't lying to me.
you were definitely lying to yourself.
Yeah.
But I'm…
I'm so sorry you heard it like that.
Yeah. that was. uh…
Hearing you tell him you loved him
after you said you loved me.
- I did. I do. I--
- It's not the same though. right?
As it is with Cole.
No.
No. it's… it's not the same.
But. uh…
But being with you was really good.
No. I mean it.
Alex. you are so sweet.
and you were such a great boyfriend.
A lot of the time. though.
it felt like we were trying really hard.
Yeah. I guess.
I don't think
it's supposed to feel like that.
No. you're right.
I guess we both
just had to figure that out.
When did you get to be so wise?
I think my dad and everything
has really showed me what matters.
Hey. you don't gotta look so worried.
I'm gonna be okay.
You are?
I'm a rodeo star now. right?
Girls are gonna be all over me.
Oh. is that right?
That's the plan.
…still hitting the track. huh?
Cole. Hey. Cole.
-This is Mac.
-Hey.
Mac. like I told you.
Cole's the best we have.
If he can't knock her into shape.
nobody can.
I'm glad to hear it.
I gotta get back out there. so…
-Missing the rush. huh?
-Yeah.
When you're racing.
the speed. the crowd.
the smell of the gas.
the fact that you could die at any second.
I'm telling you. there's nothing like it.
Hey. don't you give him any ideas.
I need you here.
So. you like cars.
Hell. you'd love it.
You should come down sometime
after you're done fixing Evangeline.
Uh… it's my grandmother's name.
-Ah.
-Yeah.
I have a whole lot of cars.
but she's my favorite.
I guess I'm sentimental that way. huh?
Right. Sure.
I'll. uh… I'll do my best.
Tony said.
♪ Every night… ♪
Parker. Benny. Jordan.
can you come down here. please?
Okay. I'm coming!
Hey. Nathan. you busy?
♪ In my head ♪
♪ Do they care? ♪
♪ Do they ever even wonder? ♪
♪ Do they wonder? ♪
Hi. honey.
♪ Open up the door
And let your darkness… ♪
What are you guys doing here?
Is everything okay? What's going on?
We're gonna fix the fence.
Come on.
You don't have to do
everything on your own. Mom.
Yeah. we wanted to help.
And we brought hot chocolate and pastries.
Who needs gloves?
I never forget my gloves.
All right. I'll supervise pastries
while they fix the fence.
Your favorite.
♪ The people. the people… ♪
Hot chocolate!
- Don't eat the whole thing.
- It's so hot
Who wants one? Hot chocolate?
Oh. thank you.
You know you didn't have to do this.
Yes. we did.
You're the best.
Wait. Did you…
No.
-Oh my God.
-Hello.
- Dad!
- Hello!
Gentle! Gentle!
- Hey.
- Hi.
Hi.
-What are you doing here?
-Dr. Segil said I could go home.
So I called Will
and wanted to surprise everyone.
Come on. Bring it in. Bring it in.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Can I get you anything else?
- No.
No. I am all set. Thank you.
I mean. Katherine brought me enough
blankets to host a slumber party. so…
Um…
I'm really sorry that I didn't come
to see you at the hospital.
After what happened to you.
I can't imagine you want
to spend one more minute in a hospital.
So you do not owe me an apology.
Oh. and I loved the smoothies.
-You did?
-I love that you made 'em for me.
So thank you.
Hey. Jackie. listen. Um…
This has been so hard on all of us.
Don't waste another second
feeling guilty. all right?
We all just need to get back to living
in the moment
and… and definitely with no regrets.
Okay?
Hi.
That was a… good thing you did before.
For my mom.
Yeah. well. we've all been so distant.
I think we needed
to spend some time together.
You know. like… like. really together.
Yeah. Well… it worked.
Yeah. and now that your dad's home.
maybe we can all go back to normal.
Yeah. Maybe.
Are you busy?
Um… not anymore.
Would you come with me?
Um… sure.
What are we doing here?
You'll see.
What… what's going on?
Why… why are we here?
Do you remember?
You brought me here
when I needed somewhere to go.
Of course I remember.
We've been so wrapped up in things lately.
you know. with your dad
and with what happened. I…
I wanted to bring you somewhere beautiful.
somewhere that meant something.
I know you're trying
to make me feel better.
And I know what we said.
but I can't do this with you.
I don't want to be friends.
I don't want to be friends either.
What?
I know I said that we couldn't
and that it wasn't the right time before.
but now might be all that we have.
♪ I've been chasing this for years ♪
♪ My legs don't work… ♪
And I think it's okay
to put ourselves first for once.
♪ You're scared that I will disappear… ♪
I want to be with you. Cole.
♪ If only you knew… ♪
Now.
♪ You could take a piece of my heart
You could rip it up ♪
♪ You could fall so out of love ♪
♪ You could do whatever you want… ♪
Really?
Really.
♪ I'll always follow
Never let you be alone ♪
♪ I'd have no shoes on my feet ♪
♪ I'd go till they bleed
If I'm what you need ♪
♪ I'm running on ♪
♪ Home to you. you ♪
♪ Oh. you. you ♪
♪ If loving you
Is the last thing I do. do ♪
♪ I'd live true. true… ♪
So how are we gonna do this?
I have no idea.
♪ As long as you were mine
At least one time ♪
♪ I'm running on ♪
♪ Home to you. you ♪
♪ Oh. you. you ♪
♪ Tell me all the reasons why ♪
♪ You're overthinking all of my actions ♪
♪ Yeah. I can't fake attraction ♪
♪ I can help you ease your mind ♪
♪ Want you to feel true satisfaction ♪
♪ I'll show you some passion ♪
♪ You could take a piece of my heart
You could rip it up ♪
♪ You could fall so out of love ♪
♪ You could do whatever you want
And I'd never leave ♪
♪ I'd be whatever you need ♪
♪ No matter the places you go ♪
♪ I'll always follow
Never let you be alone ♪
♪ I'd have no shoes on my feet ♪
♪ I'd go till they bleed
If I'm what you need ♪
♪ I'm running on ♪
♪ Home to you. you ♪
♪ Oh. you. you ♪
♪ If loving you
Is the last thing I do. do ♪
♪ I'd live true. true♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm